var questions = [
  [
    {
      "question":
          "Looking at the image above, on what stock exchange can an investor buy this stock?",
      "answers": [
        "NYSE",
        "XETRA",
        "NasdaqGS",
        "AUCTE",
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 0,
    },
    {
      "question":
          "What is the ticker of the stock presented on the above image?",
      "answers": [
        "MP",
        "BA",
        "MBG.DE",
        "MSFT",
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 1,
    },
    {
      "question": "To what industry does the stock presented above belong?",
      "answers": [
        "Aerospace",
        "Defense",
        "Auto Manufacturers",
        "Software - Infrastructure",
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 3,
    },
    {
      "question":
          "Looking at the statistics presented above, would you say this stock is a growth or a value stock?",
      "answers": [
        "growth",
        "value",
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 0,
    },
    {
      "question":
          "Looking at the provided above measures, we can say that this stock is …",
      "answers": [
        "very overvalued",
        "moderately overvalued",
        "very undervalued",
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 1,
    },
    {
      "question":
          "Looking at the financials of this particular share we can say that (choose 2 correct answers)",
      "answers": [
        "the earnings of the company have been growing steadily over the past four years.",
        "the revenue of the company have been decreasing steadily over the past four years.",
        "the costs associated with running the company have been decreasing over the past four years.",
        "the costs associated with running the company have been increasing over the past four years.",
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 3,
    },
    {
      "question": "Looking at the above data, we can say that this stock is:",
      "answers": [
        "much less volatile than the stock market.",
        "about as volatile as the stock market.",
        "much more volatile than the stock market.",
        "we don’t have the necessary information.",
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 2,
    },
    {
      "question":
          "Looking at the following data we can conclude that buying this stock, when there is high inflation, and thus high interest rates is a …",
      "answers": [
        "good idea.",
        "bad idea.",
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 1,
    },
    {
      "question":
          "Looking at the statistics presented above, would you say this stock is a growth or a value stock?",
      "answers": [
        "growth",
        "value",
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 0,
    },
    {
      "question":
          "If you were to invest \$200K in the following company, you would receive … in dividends annually (assuming you can buy fraction of shares)",
      "answers": [
        "\$4.60K",
        "\$9.20K",
        "\$2.40K",
        "\$4.80K",
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 3,
    }
  ]
];
